okay so we're going to evaluate this
definite integral this is a polynomial
so we're just going to use the power
rule so we have the constant 2 we bring
down the X and this 3 right here we add
1 to it and we also divide by that
number plus and then we're going to do
the same thing for this one we have the
constant three we're going to add 1 to
the 2 and then we're going to divide by
that 3 plus 1 is 4 so both of these will
change into four and two plus one is
three so both of these will change into
three two over four can reduce into one
over two and three over three cancel
each other out leaving us with just X
cubed and then we're going to evaluate
all of this from one to three and one
and the three come from here what this
means to evaluate is we're going to plug
in 3 for the X's giving us three to the
fourth over 2 plus 3 cubed and we're
going to subtract whatever we get when
we plug in one there'll be one to the
fourth over 2 plus 1 cubed three to the
fourth is equal to 81 and 3 cubed is
equal to 27. on this side one to the
fourth is just one and one cubed is just
one and then one plus a half is equal to
1.5 81 over 2 is equal to 40.5 now we
can get rid of these parentheses 40.5
plus 27 is 6 7.5 minus 1.5 which gives
us 66. and that's the answer to our
question this integral is equal to 66.
how exciting this problem right here is
number seven on this page I have on
andymath.com if you guys want to try
more of these the link is in the
description